(Leonard:)We're actually
scanning equations
(Leonard:)and getting good results.
(Sheldon:)Oh, well then,
by all means, carry on.
(Sheldon:)I wouldn't want
to impede your progress.
(Leonard:)Howard, did you solve
the install time problem yet?
(Howard:)No. It's a little tricky.
(Howard:)I'm gonna try having it pick up
the libraries dyn...
(Leonard:)What are you doing?!
(Sheldon:)Playing the theremin.
(Leonard:)No. I mean, what are you
doing with a theremin?
(Sheldon:)Playing it.
(Sheldon:)I've loved the theremin
from the first moment
I heard the original
Star Trek theme.
(Sheldon:)And it's been killing me
(Sheldon:)that it just sits in my closet,
gathering dust.
(Leonard:)Sheldon!
We're working here!
(Sheldon:)That's all right.